swaggsauce.com 2019-09-11

# Privacy Policy Swagg Sauce

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting swaggsauce.com This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this website. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**  
Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie / Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**  
Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Distributor Keyword and Domain Policy**

You are not allowed to bid on our AZ Swagg Sauce LLC. trademark names, renditions thereof and their derivatives. We police keyword bidding on the below terms regularly both domestically and internationally, and in order to remain in compliance with our terms of service, we'd like to inform you of the following restrictions on keyword bidding:

Publishers and international distributors are prohibited from bidding on Swagg Sauce and any variations including misspellings, alternate spellings, alternate spacing, or any phrases that include these terms.

International customers or distributors may not use our brand name or domain name, or any variation, similar terms or misspelling of our brand name, as the display domain in any search advertisement.

International customers or distributors may not use our brand name(s) or domain name, or any variation, similar terms or misspelling of our brand name in PPC ad copy without prior approval.

You may not register any domain name that contains our brand name, misspellings of our brand name or variations of our brand name.

**You are Prohibited from Direct Linking to our Website**  
We understand that these keywords may drive traffic to your site and are prepared to work with you to identify alternative ways to maximize the relationship and marketing opportunities for you. We appreciate your understanding in this matter

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**We may change this Notice from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Notice on our Site, at www.swaggsauce.com If we make any changes to this Notice that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site.**
